workato.com 2019-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Workato

At Workato, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“Workato”, “Company”, “us” or “we”), we respect and protect the privacy of visitors to our website, www.workato.com and the other websites under the workato.com domain (collectively, the “Sites”), and our customers who use our SaaS application integration platform, tools, mobile applications and related services (together with the Sites, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect visitors’ and customers’ (“Users”) information as part of the Service. Any discussion of your use of the Service in this Policy is meant to include your visits and other interactions with the Sites and Services, whether or not you are a user of Workato’s SaaS application integration platform. 

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service. By using the Service, you do hereby warrant and represent that 1) you have read, understood and agreed to all terms and conditions stated herein, including our Terms of Service, available at [www.workato.com/legal/terms-of-service](https://www.workato.com/legal/terms-of-service), incorporated herein by reference, which govern the use of the Service, and 2) you are giving Workato permission to use and store such information consistent with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. 

## Personal Information We Collect

We collect Personal Information about you when you provide such information directly to us, when third parties such as our business partners or service providers provide us with Personal Information about you, or when Personal Information about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our Services. Following is a description of the types of data we collect and the purposes of collection and processing. 

### Information We Collect Directly From You

#### Essential Account Data

We receive Personal Information directly from you when you provide it to us as part of creating an account, including at least: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Password

These data are processed in order to provide you with Services and secure access to your account. 

### Optional Account Data

As part of creating and maintaining an account with us, you may voluntarily submit additional information, including: 

  * Phone number
  * Role/Title
  * Company name
  * Company size
  * Username
  * Additional notification email addresses
  * Profile photo

Optional Account Data is used for various purposes: 

  1. Username, Company name and profile picture are collected so that you can better and more easily identify yourself to other users on the site.
  2. Phone number is processed so that we can communicate with you about the Services and contact you about Service announcements, updates or offers.
  3. Company title and company size is used by us to understand our user base and for direct marketing purposes.
  4. Notification email address(es) are processed in order to provide notifications to you as part of the Service.

### Contact Information

We may collect contact information for both present and prospective customers including name, address, phone number, title and company name, from various sources, including offline marketing activities. 

We process this information for marketing purposes and to provide support to present and prospective customers. 

### Billing Information

For customers who pay by credit card, we will also collect payment information and will associate it with a Stripe Subscription ID. (We do not store any payment card information ourselves; payment card data is collected and retained by our subprocessor for this information, Stripe. We retain only the Subscription ID). 

For other paid customers we will collect and maintain billing information (outside of the web site). 

For all paid customers, we maintain a record of Service subscriptions, invoices and payments. 

Billing information and payment records are processed in order to provide Services to our paid customers and to comply with legal and contractual requirements. 

### Connection Data

If you access our Site or Service through a third-party connection or log-in or connect an application to Workato, that third party you connected with may pass certain information about your use of its service to Workato. This information could include, but is not limited to, the User ID associated with your account, an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that third-party service. 

Connection Data is processed in order to provide application connectivity, which is part of the Service. 

### Online Form, Email and Chat Data

When you fill out an online form, for example to subscribe to a newsletter, or engage in email or online chat communications with us, you may voluntarily supply us contact and other information and we may also retain a record of any communications with you or activities you perform. 

Data from these sources is processed in order to supply you with information that you request from us, and may be used for direct marketing and analytic purposes. 

### Event Data

When you register for a Workato event, we will collect contact information from you and when you attend, we will retain a record of your participation. 

Event subscription data is collected in order to provide you with access to events that you have requested. We may also use your contact information for direct marketing purposes. Event attendance data is processed by us to better understand our user base and for marketing purposes. 

### Support Ticket Data

When you submit a support ticket through our systems, we will collect company and contact data, and record activity related to your request. 

Information submitted as part of support tickets is processed by us in order to provide help to you in using the Service, to contact you about your request(s), and to improve our products and services. 

### Blogs and Community Forums

The Service offers publicly-accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information provided in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. If you elect to post something in a public area of our Service, any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other Users have copied or saved that information. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@workato.com](mailto:privacy@workato.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information. 

From time to time, we post customer testimonials on the Sites which may contain Personal Information. We obtain the customers’ consent to post their names along with their testimonials. 

Information submitted by you to our blogs and community forums is processed by us in order to help users report and resolve problems with the Service, to communicate with users of the Service, and to improve our products and services. 

### Information We Receive From Third Party Sources

Some third parties provide us with Personal Information about you, such as the following: 

  * **Account information for third party services:** If you interact with a third party service when using our Services, such as if you use a third party service to log-in to our Services (Slack, Google, Salesforce, Office 365, Intuit or Infusionsoft), or if you share content from our Services through a third party social media service, the third party service will send us information about you, such as information from your public profile, if the third party service and your account settings allow such sharing. The information we receive will depend on the policies and your account settings with the third party service. 

We process this information in order to provide Single Sign-On, which is part of our Services. 

We may also receive information associated with your use of the website from third-party software: 

  * **Augmented tracking data:** If you visit our site and your email or other identifying data is known from interactions with our own site or with other sites, then our third-party service providers may supply additional information to us, associated with your site usage history. This information could include your name, social media user id(s) and profiles, if known and publicly available. 

We process this information in order to better understand our website users and improve our Service, and may use it for direct marketing purposes. 

### Information We Automatically Collect When You Use Our Services

Some Personal Information is automatically collected when you visit our site or use our Services, through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies. See our [Cookie Policy](https://www.workato.com/legal/cookie-policy) for a description of these technologies and your rights and options with respect to them. 

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Workato may use Personal Information provided to operate, improve upon, and personalize the Service, for billing identification and authentication, to contact and communicate with you about the Service and your use of the Service, to support use of the Service, to send marketing materials (subject to your opt-out option), for research purposes, and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service. We may also combine your Personal Information with third-party analytics information to build a broader profile of our individual Users so that we can serve you better and provide custom, personalized content and information. Additionally, we may use the Personal Information we collect for identification and authentication and fraud prevention, to analyze Site usage and improve the Service, for internal market research, troubleshooting problems, to enforce our Terms of Service, and as otherwise set forth in this Policy. Note that we will never email you to ask for your account information; if you receive such an email, please forward it to  [help@workato.com](mailto:help@workato.com). 

Workato may use your cell phone number to call or text you in order to provide the Service. If you would like more information about our policy, or to opt out, please review our Terms of Service. 

We use financial information solely as authorized by you in accordance with the Service, in order to process your payments. 

### Third-Party Processors

Workato shares Personal Information with its third party service providers (such as its credit card processors and hosting partners) to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other services we use to operate the Service and maintain a high quality user experience. 

We use third party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. 

Workato may store Personal Information in third-party marketing, CRM and mail-management software, in order to facilitate interactions with users or potential customers. 

In all situations where Workato discloses Personal Information to third parties acting as service providers or "agents" on behalf of Workato, Workato will require the recipient to protect and only use Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We do not permit our service providers to use the Personal Information we share for their marketing purposes. 

### Analytics and Logs

We may collect and use the analytic information from our own systems and from third parties together with your Personal Information to build a broader profile of our individual Users so that we can serve you better. 

Workato gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses as well as browser, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, search terms, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. Occasionally, we may connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files, as necessary to improve the Service for individual customers. Otherwise, we generally use this information as we would any Usage Data, to analyze trends, administer and maintain the Service, or track usage of various features within the Service. 

### Other Information Sharing

In addition to the purposes described above, we disclose Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, on legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations or our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

We may share information, including Personal Information with any member of the Workato which includes any entity that controls, is controlled by, or under common control with Workato. 

## Workato Recipes

Users of the Service may author, reuse or modify Recipes containing automated integration steps. These may be shared with other users on the Workato Site. When any Recipe is made available to other users, personal data is removed from it, as is connection information to external systems. Recipes may be accessed by Workato, and non-personal Recipe Information may be accessed by other authorized Users of the Service, under the terms of our current Service Agreement, in order to enhance and improve the usability of the Service. 

## Customer Data

The Workato Service allows users to connect to third-party applications, to periodically or on-demand pull data from those applications into Workato’s servers, and to pass data from the Workato Service onward to other third-party applications. 

These transfers are done only under the direction of, and under the sole control of, Workato users. By using the Service, you warrant that Workato has your permission to perform any such transfers on your behalf, notwithstanding that these may contain personal data, and may cross international borders. Workato does not control the privacy practices of applications to or from which you may transfer data, and you warrant that when transferring Customer Data, you are accepting the privacy terms to which those applications subscribe. 

Customer Data may be stored in our systems temporarily as part of processing and retained for a limited time to support Service features such as history logging and error recovery. 

Workato protects Customer Data using commercially feasible methods from interception or alteration. 

Workato will not examine or distribute any Customer Data except as provided in our Terms of Service, or as required by law. Workato may however use automated tools to examine Customer Data in aggregate, in order to improve the Service. 

## Links to Other Websites

The Service contains links to websites and applications other than the Service, including websites and applications operated by affiliates and other third parties. Please be aware that we do not determine and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of websites and applications operated by third parties. Your browsing and interaction on any third party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Service, and read the privacy statements of third party websites and applications linked to the Service. Workato does not endorse and is not responsible for the practices of third parties or their websites or applications. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and we do not control any third parties that you authorize to access your User Content or Recipe Content. If you are using a third party website or service and you allow such a third party access to your User Content or Recipe Content, you do so at your own risk. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Service. 

## Choice

We process and store information on behalf of our customers. You may decline to submit any Personal Information through the Service, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you. Please refer to your mobile device or browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. Note that disabling cookies on your mobile device or browser may prevent us or our business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Service. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Service. If you are a Workato customer and would like to opt-out of getting marketing communications from Workato please contact us at [privacy@workato.com](mailto:privacy@workato.com) in choice section. Requests to opt-out of transfers to our third-party vendors may also be submitted, but limitations on data sharing may make it difficult or impossible to provide the Service after an opt-out. 

## Correcting and Updating Your Information

Customers may update or change the Personal Information they have provided Workato by logging into the Service and providing such additional information where applicable. If you are our customer and would like to gain access to, or request deletion of information we have collected as data controllers, please contact us at [privacy@workato.com](mailto:privacy@workato.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to respond to such queries within 30 business days but are not liable for any failure to do so. 

Workato has no direct relationship with the individuals, or companies with whom our customers may interact using the Service. Any such individual seeking access to, or who would like to correct, amend, or delete data which may be stored in the Service should direct his query to the applicable Workato customer acting as the data controller for such information. 

## Do Not Track

We do not track or respond to browser “Do Not Track” Requests. 

## Data Retention

Workato will retain Personal Information we process on behalf of our customers or collect directly from our customers for as long as needed to provide Service to our customers, subject to our compliance with this Policy. We may further retain and use this Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, maintain accurate accounting, financial and other operational records, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We have established internal policies for the deletion of data from customer accounts following termination of a customer’s subscription to the Service. 

## Children's Personal Information

Workato does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through our Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information on our Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to Workato through our Service, please contact us, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from our databases. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: [privacy@workato.com](mailto:privacy@workato.com) or Workato Inc., 20450 Stevens Creek Blvd #150, Cupertino, California, 95014, Attn: Legal. 

## EU Residents

If you are an individual residing in the EU, our [EU Users Privacy Policy](https://www.workato.com//legal/eu-users-privacy-policy) terms apply to you and are hereby incorporated into this Privacy Policy. 

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may, in our sole discretion, modify or update this Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will endeavor to notify you by email or by posting a prominent notice on the Sites prior to the change becoming effective but will not be liable for any failure to do so. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Service. 

## Business Transactions

Workato may assign or transfer this Policy, and your User account and related information and data, including any Personal Information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of the business, stock or assets of, or is merged with Workato. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions or similar transactions or proceedings, provided that the recipient of such information will continue to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

## Contact Us

If you have questions regarding this Policy or about the privacy practices of Workato, please contact us by email at [privacy@workato.com](mailto:privacy@workato.com), or at: 

Workato, Inc.   
215 Castro St., Suite 300   
Mountain View, CA 94041
